# RANDY PANOPIO

randypanopio.github.io randypanopio@gmail.com 778 - 926 - 8693 Vancouver, B.C

A design oriented developer with a focus on building usable and maintainable tools. Coming from a diverse background with interests from film writing, cinematography, to history research and digital art, I try to bridge ideas and build sustainable products in all of the projects that I partake in.

## **Skills**

### Development

Languages: .NET, C#, Python, Java Web: JS, PHP, Angular, Vue, Django Version Control: Git, Perforce, GitHub, Sourcetree

#### **Content Creation**

Maya & Scripting (MayaPy, PyMEL), Photoshop, Adobe Creative Suite, 3D Modelling, Character Rigging, IK Animations, Vector and Raster Graphics

#### **Toolkits**

Unity Engine, Frostbite Engine, Procedural Content Generation, 3D Modelling, Character Rigging, FK/IK Animation, Shaders (Shader Graphs)

## **Methodologies**

Test Driven Development, Agile Methodology, Iterative Design Process, Pipeline Architecture Design, User Research Methodology

## **Education**

#### **Simon Fraser University**

Interactive Arts and Technology (SIAT), Bachelor of Science -Concentration of Interactive Systems

2015 - 2020

## **Work Experience**

# Electronic Arts Associate Technical Artist

Burnaby, British Columbia **Sept 2021 - Present** 

Worked on pipeline tool development and management to deliver art assets from content creation all the way to in game render. Supported multiple FIFA/FC titles including titles from 22, 23, FC rebrand, FIFA Online, FIFA Mobile, and unreleased incubation football titles.

- Subject matter expert on content management and worked on designing and replacing the delivery pipeline, tripling the previous workflow's throughput and reducing time it takes to run the process from a typical 10 minute cold run down to 1 minute, while introducing previously unsupported content into this automated framework.
- Worked on improving and replacing legacy pipelines, saving the team workflow capacity by up to 75% by eliminating manual workflows with automated pipelines.
- Trained and supported Technical Artists, Artists, and Management on our production workflows and tools
- Collaborated and supported cross domain teams and multiple international teams to organize, process, and deliver content into the game while maintaining production timelines
- Updated existing DCC tools and authoring new tools to improve and automate repetitive tasks from artists.

## Under the GUI Academy Inc. **Programming Instructor**

Richmond, British Columbia

Dec 2020 - June 2021

Taught children ages 7 - 16 concepts of programming through hands on Unity and website projects during weekly online class sessions.

- Introduced concepts regarding programming foundations, web development, and game design to children with various skill levels
- Volunteered creating personalized coding challenges for advanced students who showed interest in expanding their programming repertoire

# Safe Software Inc. Front-End Web Developer - Co-op

Surrey, British Columbia May 2018 - Dec 2018

Acted as a front-end developer and the primary interface designer, maintaining and building web interfaces for a suite of enterprise GIS management tools.

- Collaborated with a team of developers, product managers, and stakeholders working on a new core feature, on an enterprise web application used by over 10,000 organizations across the world
- Designed and implemented three new UI for new features built upon existing management tools with over 100 individual UI elements, within 3 design iterations and testing phase completed in the span of 4 months
- Worked in an agile and test-driven development environment, building from a hybrid web frameworks while maintaining and authoring unit tests during production